<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Victor\'s recipes</string>
    <string name="name">Victor\'s recipes</string>
    <string name="recipe">Ingredients:</string>
    <string name="recipeone"><b>Ingredients</b><![CDATA[\n\n1.3 cups all-purpose flour\n2.Two sticks unsalted butter\n3.1 tablespoon baking powder.\n4.&#189; teaspoon salt.\n5.1 &#188; cups sugar.\n6.4 large eggs, at room temperature.\n7.1 tablespoon vanilla extract.\n\n]]><b>HOW TO PREPAPE:</b>\n\n1.Preheat the oven at 185 °F (85 °C).\n\n2.Sieve flour and baking powder in a bowl.\n\n3.Beat the eggs.\n\n4.Add the sugar to the eggs and beat it properly until it becomes smooth.\n\n5.Add oil and then beat it again until smooth.\n\n6.Add the vanilla essence\n\n7.
Add the flour mixture to the batter and beat it lightly(do not use an electrical beater while beating the flour\n\n8.
Pour the batter in the tin.\n\n9.
Put the cake mixture into the oven for 1 hour.\n\n10.Take the cake out and serve.</string>
    <string name="recipefries"><b>Ingredients</b>\n\n1.Potatoes\n2.Cooking Oil\n3.Salt\n4.Flour\n5.Garlic salt\n6.Onion salt or (regular) salt\n7.Paprika\n8.Tomato Sauce\n\n<b>HOW TO PREPARE:</b>\n\n1.Slice potatoes into French fries, and place into cold water (to prevent them from turning brown while you prepare the oil).\n\n2.Heat oil in a large skillet over medium high heat.\n3.Sift the flour, garlic salt, onion salt or (regular) salt, and paprika into a large bowl and add the fries.\n\n3.Fry until golden brown and crispy\n\n4.Spice the up with your favourite sauces </string>
    <string name="reciperice"><b>Ingredients</b>\n\n1.Rice\n2.Water\n3.Salt\n4.Masala\n5.Garlic Powder\n6.Butter\n\n<b>HOW TO PREPARE:</b>\n\n1.Add 2 cups converted rice,salt,garlic powder and 4 cups of water and bring the to boil\n\n2.Reduce the heat to low and stir; cover and cook until tender for 20 minutes.\n\n3.Let it sit, covered for 5 minutes, then stir in 2 tablespoons of butter\n\n4.Season with salt </string>
    <string name="recipeomlette"><b>Ingredients</b>\n\n1.Eggs \n 2.Cooking Oil/Butter \n 3.Onions\n 4.Pepper \n 5.Salt \n\n<b>HOW TO PREPARE:</b>\n\n1.BEAT eggs, water, salt and pepper in small bowl until blended\n\n2.
HEAT butter in 6 to 8-inch nonstick omelet pan or skillet over medium-high heat until hot.\n\n3.GENTLY PUSH cooked portions from edges toward the center with inverted turner so that uncooked eggs can reach the hot pan surface.
\n\n4.Serve when hot</string>
    <string name="Author">victor kamau</string>
    <string name="client">Becky</string>
    <string name="donut">Donut</string>
</resources>
